

Contacts

+38 050 755 69 18

werbolom@gmail.com

Telegram

LinkedIn

GitHub

Portfolio

Tech Skills

- HTML5
- CSS3
- GIT
- WebPack
- JavaScript
- React.js
- Redux
- Node.jsNext.js
- Typescript

Soft skills

- Desire to constantly develop
- Quick learner
- Creativity
- Teamwork

Languages

- Ukrainian native
- English advanced
- Russian native

Oleksandr Melnychenko Full Stack Developer

Summary

I am an ambitious and young developer who strives for self-development and will not stop before any obstacles. For me, there is no ceiling that I can lean against and tell myself that I have learned enough. I have a lot of experience in communication with other people, as this is the key to successful teamwork. Analytical mindset has always helped me solve any problems both at work and in life. Solving problems has always been interesting and exciting for me and has always been one of my favorite activities.

Work Experience

Frontend Developer at Roqo Practicum

Internship

April 2024 - August 2024

- Developing project according to design using React and Typescript
- Writing unit and integration test
- · Reviewing my teammates' code
- Discussing inside team on best implemenation of features
- Working with GIT

Frontend Developer at SoftRyzen

Internship

August 2023 - September 2023

- Developing project using Next.js and Tailwind according to design
- Creating reusable components
- Working with Open Graph Protocol
- Project presentation to the client

Trainee at PBN Hill+Knowlton Strategies

September 2021 - February 2022

- Daily monitoring
- · Translation of texts
- Surface research of the market
- Helped stop the blocking of the Ukrainian hero on Facebook

Analyst at ICM

August 2020 - February 2021

- Weekly monitoring of news
- Writing analytical note
- Searching for information in the Internet
- Prepared a well-known Ukrainian figure for an interview

Education

GOIT

Full-stack developer

March 2023 - September 2023

State University of Trade and Economics

Marketing

September 2022 - Present | Postgraduate studies

National University of 'Kyiv-Mohyla Academy'

Public Relations; Management in Healthcare

September 2020 - June 2022 | Master's degree

History and Archeology

September 2016 - June 2020 | Bachelor's degree